[{"answer": "Well, this came about as an unauthorized leak from somewhere in the investigation.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "What can you tell us about what's happened today?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, we do have the reaction from the family.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "I mean, how credibly are people taking these police reports?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, that is unfair to declare him guilty a month after the whole thing went down.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Is it unfair towards George Zimmerman to be effectively declaring him guilty?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, here's the thing.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "That \"Stand Your Ground\" thingy, that \"Stand Your Ground\" law that they have in place, I don't understand it.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "What do you feel about a justice system that has that law?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "If he then turns around and punches him, and you assume that happened, does that give anyone the right to shoot him?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "It's called \"Super Life.\"", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What's it called?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "That was beautiful.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What did you feel when you heard that?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think we've seen some things happening and some things being said about Obama that I think were sort of on the racist side.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Do you think America is more or less racist since getting its first black president?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "I find that very interesting.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What do you think about that?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "No, I really don't.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "But should they be allowed to be vigilantes?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Do you feel if it had been, for argument's sake, a 17- year-old white boy and a black man who had killed him, would we be in the same position?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I truly believe that.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "You really believe that?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Him actually using a gun?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, please, son, be careful.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What do you say to him?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "HAN: Yes.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Ridiculous, too.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "And I understand that, is, you know, I mean, it took them three days to identify him, you know?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Is to raise awareness in children and adults and everybody that you can't judge a person by what he's wearing.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "And your purpose with this -- just remind me -- is to do what?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "You shake it up like an Etch-a-Sketch.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "How's your etching and sketching?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "We're talking about big things here, folks.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "You have an Etch-a-Sketch?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, he should have problems in the Republican primary.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "How big a problem is it going to be for Mitt Romney, if he becomes the nominee, the fact that his own health plans were very similar to what Barack Obama is trying to get through?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "You know, the question unfortunately can be answered by another question, which is the best thing.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "OLE: Well, not only the law that treats black boys.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "First of all, I do want to thank you for giving me the opportunity to speak about this.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What do you think of everything that's happened in the last month?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "OLE: You know, I talked to Whitney.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Did you try and help her?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Oh my goodness, I had to cancel a New Years Eve show in Atlantic City a few years -- about two years ago.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Can you relate to that?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "She hit some of them, yeah.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Could she still hit the big notes?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you -- is your voice as good as it was, say, 20 years ago?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I'm just sad -- happy sad.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What do you feel watching that?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "When you heard that Whitney had died, did you feel that it had been a wasted life or was it an inevitably short life that had amazingly high moments?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Or both?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120326pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Of Whitney?", "qSentId": 634}]